<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>dtweb.page POSTs</title>
  <link>https://dtweb.page/post</link>
  <description>dtweb.page all blog posts</description>
  <lastBuildDate>
    Fri, 31 May 2024 19:00:00 -0700
  </lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>20000</ttl>
  <item>
    <title>Lamian Audio is dead.</title>
    <link>https://dtweb.page/post/20240531-lamian</link>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Lamian Audio was pretty fun for the most part. It came from a prior appreciation for the medium: how do you effecitvely tell a story with just audio?&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I have been told I had a nice voice for a while, and while I don't really believe that to be a pre-requisite, it was certainly an asset. I'm glad people like my voice.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Friends to lovers was by far my favourite audio to do, and it's evident by just how much I posted them. It's sweet, it's emotional, and it's &quot;real.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;But I never really went beyond that. Sure, a few &quot;enemies&quot; to lovers were there, but my audios were extremely derivative. People stayed for it, clearly. My audience affectionately called me the &quot;king of friends to lovers.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;As time went on, the audio roleplay space grew. Growth is good, and it's nice to have more people appreciate this medium, but I grew increasingly tired and unhappy with this project&mdash; and with the space in general.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I got lucky with my audience. They were quite dedicated to most anything I posted. After a while, I started posting miscellaneous content, like music, &quot;actual&quot; videos, etc. It was surprisingly well-received.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;But I was increasingly worried with the state of not only my audience, but casual listeners. &quot;Boyfriend ASMR&quot; is inherently &quot;intimate.&quot; Generally, you don't listen just for funsies. Some might have, but others listened with a specific purpose: comfort. I was one of them.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For about a year prior to this project, I heavily leaned on these audios to actually sleep in any capacity. I had gone through some things in my personal life that affected me deeply. I needed something, anything. I grew dependent on them. It was a bad time.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;And I know I'm not alone in this. When listening to these audios in a vulnerable, emotional state, you grow attached not to a person but to an avatar, a simulation. You grow accustomed to the comfort it gives you. You connect with a perfect image, because &lt;em&gt;it would never hurt you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This was my biggest concern: I was there, so how many of those listening to me would be same?&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I intentionally kept a distance from my audience. (Which should be done anyway.) I gave constant reminders to keep me accountable. Lamian Audio is not real, and it will never be real. You have to keep this mind. You must.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Do I claim to be better than other creators in the space? ...well, kind of.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Because of the pseudonymous nature of this space, you'll likely never see the face of an audio creator. It's an immersion thing, I get it.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;But it's so, so easy to look beyond the flaws of the person behind the channels&mdash; because there &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; no person behind it. It's abstracted by character art, comments, and whatever projected demeanour they market themselves as.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;It's a recipe for vulnerable minds to be taken advantage of and abused. There's a Google Doc floating around with &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; allegations of creators who would solicit sexually explicit and other abusive material from fans, including minors.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;These sick fucks are effectively given a pass, because they'll disappear and pop back up once, or if they're caught. It's so easy.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;So much of this audio content online evolved to just blatant sex bait. A provocative, borderline pornographic catalogue.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I'm not here to yuck anyone's yum, I'm really not. It's just super questionable to have this type of content on YouTube, a platform available to all ages.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&quot;Think of the children,&quot; a claim I despise as much as you do. But it's justified here: colourful anime characters, and slick graphics will catch eyes. It's a problem when those lead to unhealthy expectations of sex.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The state of r/GWA is quite controversial to someone not accustomed to this space. And it's O.K. to listen to that, it's fine. But it does no favours to a middle schooler with unsupervised internet access.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;They'll ignore the 18+ warning. Porn is mainstream. With this BookTok &quot;smut&quot; phenomenon and the already widely available &quot;tube&quot; sites, it's everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Is that bad? I don't know. I'm not trying to demonize porn as some &quot;evil force.&quot; It's not really good or bad, it just &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I fear that I've done irreperable damage to some of my more impressionable audience. I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; there are very young viewers in my audience. I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; that some have gotten unhealthily attached. It might be inherent to this medium, it might not. But it's an irrefutable fact that goes unsaid.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;How many of them prefer to listen to a simulacra of a relationship? How many will grow forever attached, terminally online, unwilling to step into the real world?&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Roleplay audios have recently seeped into the &quot;internet&quot; mainstream. The memey &quot;boyfriend hits you with a pan&quot; audios are making the rounds. It's pretty funny. But it will only grow from here.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Media literacy is on fritz. All I can do is turn off my faucet.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CRtN8Dc8IeA&quot;&gt;I posted an audio recently.&lt;/a&gt; It serves as a meta-overview of my situation. Things were nice once, but we can't go back to that. Whether you knew or not, I hurt you. We reflect and move on. We need to. It was a different time, and we'll never go back to that.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;But we can stay &quot;friends.&quot; I'm more than Lamian Audio now. Lamian Audio is dead. I'm doing cool things, and so should you.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I just hope you'll watch and grow, as will I.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
    <pubDate>
        Fri, 31 May 2024 19:00:00 -0700
    </pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>